Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Colleges, 1949 - 1974; 22 (Box 1540)
    - Part of inaugural procession. Left to Right: Prof. Chad Dunham (marshal), Mr. [Herbert] Hoover, Dr. Flemming, the Reverend Father Flynn, Dean Ficken, Lowell Thomas, Chancellor Burghstahler, the Reverend Dr. Harris, Bishop Welch [1949], 4
    - Verso: Part of inaugural procession. Left to Right: Prof. Chad Dunham (marshal), Mr. [Herbert] Hoover, Dr. Flemming, the Reverend Father Flynn, Dean Ficken, Lowell Thomas, Chancellor Burghstahler, the Reverend Dr. Harris, Bishop Welch [1949], 4-verso
    - Ex.-President Hoover delivering inaugural address at induction of Arthur Flemming, Selby Stadium, June 11, 1949, This picture also sent to Mrs. Thornburg, 5
    - Verso: Ex.-President Hoover delivering inaugural address at induction of Arthur Flemming, Selby Stadium, June 11, 1949, This picture also sent to Mrs. Thornburg, 5-verso
    - Herbert Hoover and Lowell Thomas leaving Pullman car, Union Terminal, 8 a.m., Saturday, June 11, 1949. Porter in right foreground attended Ohio Wesleyan University, 6
    - Verso: Herbert Hoover and Lowell Thomas leaving Pullman car, Union Terminal, 8 a.m., Saturday, June 11, 1949. Porter in right foreground attended Ohio Wesleyan University, 6-verso
    - Lowell Thomas speaking to Mrs. Arthur Flemming and Herbert Hoover, Alumni luncheon, Edwards Gym, OWU, June 11, 1949, 7
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas speaking to Mrs. Arthur Flemming and Herbert Hoover, Alumni luncheon, Edwards Gym, OWU, June 11, 1949, 7-verso
    - Mr. Hoover and Dr. Flemming on the lawn at the President's residence, Ohio Wesleyan University, Delaware, Ohio, June 11, 1949, 8
    - Verso: Mr. Hoover and Dr. Flemming on the lawn at the President's residence, Ohio Wesleyan University, Delaware, Ohio, June 11, 1949, 8-verso
    - Arthur Fleming, H.H. [Herbert Hoover] and LT at Ohio Wesleyan, 9
    - Verso: Arthur Fleming, H.H. [Herbert Hoover] and LT at Ohio Wesleyan, 9-verso
    - First row reading from left to right: Dale Carnegie, Dr. Harry G. Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Dr. Linus Pauling, Dr. Clarence Hall, Homer M. Pace; Second row: J. Crockett Farnell, Louis Wellhouse, Jr., James L. Ferman, C. Milo ega, David E. Smiley, Dr. E. C. Nance (president of the University of Tampa, Thelma Jones (dean of women), Dr. M. C. Rhodes (dean of administration), and Dr. H. G. Baker (dean of men), 10
    - Note: First row reading from left to right: Dale Carnegie, Dr. Harry G. Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Dr. Linus Pauling, Dr. Clarence Hall, Homer M. Pace; Second row: J. Crockett Farnell, Louis Wellhouse, Jr., James L. Ferman, C. Milo Vega, David E. Smiley, Dr. E. C. Nance (president of the University of Tampa, Thelma Jones (dean of women), Dr. M. C. Rhodes (dean of administration), and Dr. H. G. Baker (dean of men), 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others at graduation], 12
    - U. of Neb., ex. Gov. Peterson at mike, Univ. Pres. [University of Nebraska, ex-Governor Peterson at microphone, University President at left], 13
    - Verso: U. of Neb., ex. Gov. Peterson at mike, Univ. Pres. [University of Nebraska, ex-Governor Peterson at microphone, University President at left], 13-verso
    - U. of Neb., ex. Gov. Peterson at mike, Univ. Pres. [University of Nebraska, ex-Governor Peterson at microphone, University President at left], 14
    - Univ. of Neb. [University of Nebraska], 15
    - Verso: Univ. of Neb. [University of Nebraska], 15-verso
    - Univ. of Neb. [University of Nebraska], 16
    - Verso: Univ. of Neb. [University of Nebraska], 16-verso
    - At Lafayette Univ., Pres. Ralph Cooper Hutchinson and [Fiorello] La Guardia [second from left], 17
    - Verso: At Lafayette Univ., Pres. Ralph Cooper Hutchinson and [Fiorello] La Guardia [second from left], 17-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas is hooded for the Doctor of Political Science Degree at the Founders' Day Convocation of Marietta College Feb. 14. President W. Bay Irvine, at left, presented him for the degree and Dean Merrill R. Patterson cited him for his many professional accomplishments, 18
    - Note: Mr. Lowell Thomas is hooded for the Doctor of Political Science Degree at the Founders' Day Convocation of Marietta College Feb. 14. President W. Bay Irvine, at left, presented him for the degree and Dean Merrill R. Patterson cited him for his many professional accomplishments, 19
    - Valparaiso Univ. Chancellor with medallion, 20
    - Verso: Valparaiso Univ. Chancellor with medallion, 20-verso
    - Bringham Young University, BYU Commencement, 21
    - Verso: Bringham Young University, BYU Commencement, 21-verso
    - Chicago-Kent College of Law, LLD to LT, 22
    - Verso: Chicago-Kent College of Law, LLD to LT, 22-verso
    - Chicago-Kent College of Law, LLD to LT, 23
    - Verso: Chicago-Kent College of Law, LLD to LT, 23-verso
    - Dan Burke, Dr. L. F. Coor, Pres of U of Vt. [President of the University of Vermont], [Lowell Thomas], Dr. Chas Houston, 24
    - Verso: Dan Burke, Dr. L. F. Coor, Pres of U of Vt. [President of the University of Vermont], [Lowell Thomas], Dr. Chas Houston, 24-verso
    - U. of Vermont [University of Vermont], 25
    - Verso: U. of Vermont [University of Vermont], 25-verso
    - 1930s Boston Univ. Honorary degree, [?] Watson, Juan Trippe, 26
    - Verso: 1930s Boston Univ. Honorary degree, [?] Watson, Juan Trippe, 26-verso
  Box 1541 - Box 1544
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1545 - Box 1548
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1549 - Box 1552
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1553 - Box 1556
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1557 - Box 1560
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1561 - Box 1565
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6